Guide to the Archives Union File Part 2, Section 1: Boxes 1-65 1872-1976
Archives Union File Part 2, Section 1: Boxes 1-65
- Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1941; Publication (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1941; Publication (Box 60, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.75:no.12 (1941: Dec.)
- Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1942; Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1942; Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.76:no.1 (1942: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1942; Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.76:no.2 (1942: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1942; Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.76:no.3 (1942: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1942; Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.76:no.4 (1942: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1942; Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.76:no.5 (1942: May)
  - Item 6: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1942; Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.76:no.6 (1942: June)
  - Item 7: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1942; Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.76:no.7 (1942: July)
  - Item 8: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1942; Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.76:no.8 (1942: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1942; Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.76:no.9 (1942: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1942; Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.76:no.10 (1942: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1942; Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.76:no.11 (1942: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1942; Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.76:no.12 (1942: Dec.)
- Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1943; Publication (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1943; Publication (Box 61, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.77:no.1 (1943: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1943; Publication (Box 61, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.77:no.2 (1943: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1943; Publication (Box 61, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.77:no.3 (1943: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1943; Publication (Box 61, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.77:no.4 (1943: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1943; Publication (Box 61, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.77:no.5 (1943: May)
  - Item 6: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1943; Publication (Box 61, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.77:no.6 (1943: June)
  - Item 7: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1943; Publication (Box 61, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.77:no.7 (1943: July)
  - Item 8: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1943; Publication (Box 61, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.77:no.8 (1943: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1943; Publication (Box 61, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.77:no.9 (1943: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1943; Publication (Box 61, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.77:no.10 (1943: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1943; Publication (Box 61, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.77:no.11 (1943: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1943; Publication (Box 61, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.77:no.12 (1943: Dec.)
- Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1944; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1944; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.78:no.1 (1944: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1944; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.78:no.2 (1944: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1944; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.78:no.3 (1944: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1944; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.78:no.4 (1944: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1944; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.78:no.5 (1944: May)
  - Item 6: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1944; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.78:no.6 (1944: June)
  - Item 7: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1944; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.78:no.7 (1944: July)
  - Item 8: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1944; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.78:no.8 (1944: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1944; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.78:no.9 (1944: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1944; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.78:no.10 (1944: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1944; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.78:no.11 (1944: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1944; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.78:no.12 (1944: Dec.)
- Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1945; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1945; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.79:no.1 (1945: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1945; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.79:no.2 (1945: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1945; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.79:no.3 (1945: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1945; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.79:no.4 (1945: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1945; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.79:no.5 (1945: May)
  - Item 6: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1945; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.79:no.6 (1945: June)
  - Item 7: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1945; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.79:no.7 (1945: July)
  - Item 8: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1945; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.79:no.8 (1945: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1945; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.79:no.9 (1945: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1945; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.79:no.10 (1945: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1945; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.79:no.11 (1945: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1945; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.79:no.12 (1945: Dec.)
- Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1946; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1946; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.80:no.1 (1946: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1946; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.80:no.2 (1946: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1946; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.80:no.3 (1946: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1946; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.80:no.4 (1946: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1946; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.80:no.5 (1946: May)
  - Item 6: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1946; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.80:no.6 (1946: June)
  - Item 7: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1946; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.80:no.7 (1946: July)
  - Item 8: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1946; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.80:no.8 (1946: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1946; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.80:no.9 (1946: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1946; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.80:no.10 (1946: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1946; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.80:no.11 (1946: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1946; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.80:no.12 (1946: Dec.)
- Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1947; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1947; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.81:no.1 (1947: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1947; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.81:no.2 (1947: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1947; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.81:no.3 (1947: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1947; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.81:no.4 (1947: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1947; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.81:no.5 (1947: May)
  - Item 6: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1947; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.81:no.6 (1947: June)
  - Item 7: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1947; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.81:no.7 (1947: July)
  - Item 8: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1947; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.81:no.8 (1947: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1947; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.81:no.9 (1947: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1947; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.81:no.10 (1947: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1947; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.81:no.11 (1947: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1947; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.81:no.12 (1947: Dec.)
- Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1948; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1948; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.82:no.1 (1948: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1948; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.82:no.2 (1948: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1948; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.82:no.3 (1948: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1948; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.82:no.4 (1948: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1948; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.82:no.5 (1948: May)
  - Item 6: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1948; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.82:no.6 (1948: June)
  - Item 7: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1948; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.82:no.7 (1948: July)
  - Item 8: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1948; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.82:no.8 (1948: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1948; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.82:no.9 (1948: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1948; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.82:no.10 (1948: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1948; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.82:no.11 (1948: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1948; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.82:no.12 (1948: Dec.)
- Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1949; Publication (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1949; Publication (Box 64, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.83:no.1 (1949: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1949; Publication (Box 64, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.83:no.10 (1949: Oct.)
  - Item 3: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1949; Publication (Box 64, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.83:no.11 (1949: Nov.)
  - Item 4: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1949; Publication (Box 64, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.83:no.12 (1949: Dec.)
  - Item 5: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1949; Publication (Box 64, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.83:no.2 (1949: Feb.)
  - Item 6: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1949; Publication (Box 64, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.83:no.3 (1949: Mar.)
  - Item 7: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1949; Publication (Box 64, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.83:no.4 (1949: Apr.)
  - Item 8: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1949; Publication (Box 64, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.83:no.5 (1949: May)
  - Item 9: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1949; Publication (Box 64, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.83:no.6 (1949: June)
  - Item 10: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1949; Publication (Box 64, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.83:no.7 (1949: July)
  - Item 11: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1949; Publication (Box 64, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.83:no.8 (1949: Aug.)
  - Item 12: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1949; Publication (Box 64, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.83:no.9 (1949: Sept.)
- Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1950; Publication (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1950; Publication (Box 64, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.84:no.1 (1950: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1950; Publication (Box 64, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.84:no.2 (1950: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1950; Publication (Box 64, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.84:no.3 (1950: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1950; Publication (Box 64, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.84:no.4 (1950: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1950; Publication (Box 64, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.84:no.5 (1950: May)
  - Item 6: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1950; Publication (Box 64, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.84:no.6 (1950: June)
  - Item 7: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1950; Publication (Box 64, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.84:no.7 (1950: July)
  - Item 8: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1950; Publication (Box 64, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.84:no.8 (1950: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1950; Publication (Box 64, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.84:no.9 (1950: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1950; Publication (Box 64, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.84:no.10 (1950: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1950; Publication (Box 64, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.84:no.11 (1950: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1950; Publication (Box 64, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.84:no.12 (1950: Dec.)
- Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1951; Publication (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1951; Publication (Box 64, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.85:no.1 (1951: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1951; Publication (Box 64, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.85:no.2 (1951: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1951; Publication (Box 64, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.85:no.3 (1951: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1951; Publication (Box 64, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.85:no.4 (1951: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1951; Publication (Box 64, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.85:no.5 (1951: May)
  - Item 6: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1951; Publication (Box 64, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.85:no.6 (1951: June)
  - Item 7: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1951; Publication (Box 64, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.85:no.7 (1951: July)
  - Item 8: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1951; Publication (Box 64, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.85:no.8 (1951: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1951; Publication (Box 64, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.85:no.9 (1951: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1951; Publication (Box 64, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.85:no.10 (1951: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1951; Publication (Box 64, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.85:no.11 (1951: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1951; Publication (Box 64, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.85:no.12 (1951: Dec.)
- Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1952; Publication (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1952; Publication (Box 65, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.86:no.1 (1952: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1952; Publication (Box 65, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.86:no.2 (1952: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1952; Publication (Box 65, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.86:no.3 (1952: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1952; Publication (Box 65, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.86:no.4 (1952: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1952; Publication (Box 65, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.86:no.5 (1952: May)
  - Item 6: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1952; Publication (Box 65, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.86:no.6 (1952: June)
  - Item 7: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1952; Publication (Box 65, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.86:no.7 (1952: July)
  - Item 8: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1952; Publication (Box 65, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.86:no.8 (1952: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1952; Publication (Box 65, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.86:no.9 (1952: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1952; Publication (Box 65, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.86:no.10 (1952: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1952; Publication (Box 65, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.86:no.11 (1952: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1952; Publication (Box 65, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.86:no.12 (1952: Dec.)
- Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1953; Publication (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1953; Publication (Box 65, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.87:no.1 (1953: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1953; Publication (Box 65, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.87:no.2 (1953: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1953; Publication (Box 65, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.87:no.3 (1953: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1953; Publication (Box 65, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.87:no.4 (1953: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1953; Publication (Box 65, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.87:no.5 (1953: May)
  - Item 6: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1953; Publication (Box 65, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.87:no.6 (1953: June)
  - Item 7: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1953; Publication (Box 65, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.87:no.7 (1953: July)
  - Item 8: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1953; Publication (Box 65, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.87:no.8 (1953: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1953; Publication (Box 65, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.87:no.9 (1953: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1953; Publication (Box 65, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.87:no.10 (1953: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1953; Publication (Box 65, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.87:no.11 (1953: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1953; Publication (Box 65, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.87:no.12 (1953: Dec.)
- Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1954; Publication (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1954; Publication (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.88:no.1 (1954: Jan.)
  - Item 2: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1954; Publication (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.88:no.2 (1954: Feb.)
  - Item 3: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1954; Publication (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.88:no.3 (1954: Mar.)
  - Item 4: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1954; Publication (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.88:no.4 (1954: Apr.)
  - Item 5: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1954; Publication (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.88:no.5 (1954: May)
  - Item 6: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1954; Publication (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.88:no.6 (1954: June)
  - Item 7: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1954; Publication (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.88:no.7 (1954: July)
  - Item 8: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1954; Publication (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.88:no.8 (1954: Aug.)
  - Item 9: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1954; Publication (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.88:no.9 (1954: Sept.)
  - Item 10: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1954; Publication (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.88:no.10 (1954: Oct.)
  - Item 11: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1954; Publication (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.88:no.11 (1954: Nov.)
  - Item 12: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1954; Publication (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.88:no.12 (1954: Dec.)